[Music]
good morning besties happy Sunday it is
like 9:00 a.m. and we're going to spend
the Sunday together I thought I would do
like a Sunday reset video and just take
you through my day like my typical
Sunday routine prepping for the week the
only thing about this that is like an
every week type of thing is resetting
the house on Sundays which I actually
haven't done in like 3 or 4 weeks like
I'll I'll minorly do it but today the
house like really needs a Sunday reset
and I just kind of fell off and I
realized I hadn't filmed a Sunday reset
video in like over a year I think since
2023 we are going to deep clean the
entire house kind of get it ready do
some grocery shopping honestly just hang
out I don't really have plans today but
I thought I would still Vlog first
things first is coffee okay I'm actually
going to do my lemon water first because
it's just best on an empty stomach and I
think it's been
helping I'm pretty strict about like not
drinking coffee on an empty stomach like
I just don't ever really do that because
it makes me break out it also gives me
like a weird headache at the bottom of
my like neck or around my neck I think
it's a tension headache the one day I do
allow myself to do it is Sundays cuz
it's just such a vibe to wake up make
your coffee like cook go to church just
take it slow Theo stop I also have some
nice lowii playing my goal with Sundays
is I don't really have one and I really
just like to like wake up the house in a
very peaceful way speaking of the house
I ordered a bunch of stuff last night
like home decor items that are coming in
in like the next
week I just do like warm water with half
a lemon and then this is kind of brand
new Renee introduced me to this but I
actually am pouring turmeric into the
lemon water just for like some extra
vitamins so I'll just do a few shakes of
that that and then I'll do cracked black
pepper the black pepper helps your body
absorb the turmeric and it looks like
like a golden
drink but it's really good for like skin
gut health immunity when you add like
the turmeric and the pepper you can also
add like ginger and stuff like you can
literally make this like a whole thing
what was I saying oh I ordered a bunch
of home decor items because decorating a
house has just been like so hard like
there's so much space it's kind kind of
overwhelming in May I'm going to have
been here for a year and I used to live
in a sad beige apartment and so when I
brought everything here I kind of like
pieced it up throughout the house I
spread it out and now I'm like
decorating all that in between I want it
to feel like super filled up and like
cozy and I just know that's going to
take longer than a year also I was
talking to you guys in my last video
about potentially redoing my room setup
but I do think I'm going to go through
with that I ordered like a bunch of
little home decor things but I'll show
you all of that when it comes in it just
reminded me cuz I was like doing that at
like midnight last night that's what I
do with my Saturday nights one thing I
miss about my well there's several
things I miss about living in an
apartment but one thing is how easy it
was to fill the space and make it feel
really cozy and homey cuz you're
literally in like a fourth of the square
footage that's just a little home update
which wasn't really an update at all cuz
nothing's here yet but I'm telling you
that things are coming in enough of me
rambling I'm going to make breakfast and
also make a coffee
[Music]
this has been the go-to BR breakfast
lately it's just avocado toast with a
slice of tomato and then Egg and I put
everything but the bagel on top and then
two slices of turkey bacon and it takes
like literally 10 minutes I love it
[Music]
guys it's Sunday which means it's sheet
washing day so I'm going to strip the
bed throw the sheets in the wash and
then I'll put them on when we get back
later and reset the house this latte
came out so good I add Honey brown sugar
and usually vanilla extract into the
espresso and then make a little ice
latte also we need to talk about how
freaking
cute these PJs are aren't they adorable
they have croissant and coffee on them
are you
joking are you joking I got them from
Lounge underwear so I'll link it down
below and I love them so so so so much I
do have an addiction to PJ sets which
you've probably noticed by now but
there's worse things to be addicted to
so
[Music]
okay I'm just going to get ready really
quickly cuz I need to leave in like 20
minutes I'm going to put my mask
on the only thing about this mask that
kind of sucks is it literally hurts my
eyes the light is so bright but I've
been trying to do it twice a day okay
let's pick an outfit you're just going
to have to excuse my appearance right
now I'm going to do this red sweater
from Reformation I'm going to do a
little white shirt under so it like
Peaks through at the top I love the way
that looks and then just jeans
[Music]
probably if you want good slick backs
but have a hard time getting this part
like really tight to your head this
stuff is life saving and I recommend it
you can get at Sephora got these cutie
little earrings from maidwell I just
realized that I always wear the same
Huggies and I was like I should add a
new pair to the rotation that's cute
also guys I switched my nails I took off
my extensions what do we think I got
this like really cute brown tortoise but
I just went back to Natural Nails I feel
like something about it very classy and
I I just had had almond nails for like
over a year I like feeling like I have
fingers again and I just like the way it
looks like I think it's really pretty
natural nail era I
guess I'm heading out this is the church
fit I just have on oh wait I think I
showed you guys Reformation sweater Cuts
tea Reformation pants and then like
these Ugg is loafer things my regular
jewelry and these sunglasses that I
think they're from L specs but I'm
running late let's go I'll see you
there I like your grandpa's shoes I know
I wanted to wear them with my head we
finished at church and we put our names
on a wait list for a restaurant so we
can eat lunch at because I have zero
things at the house we are at Kirby Lane
I think that's what it's called I've
been here once the food was all right
but the Vibes are cute and it's really
nice out today so I'm hoping that we can
sit outside Rene is here except I sent
him in because I think we got off the
weight list I love spending my Sundays
like out doing stuff like this before I
have to go home and like get serious
like preparing for the week I'm also
just getting like so excited for summer
I want summer
here so bad it's getting warm not warm
it feels like spring out which I feel
like is summer most places and I just
miss the beach and I miss it so bad I
want to go to a New England coastal town
so so badly this summer I don't think
I've ever been to New England last
summer I went to Seaside which was
really really really pretty but this
year like I want to go somewhere new but
same Vibe type of thing and I'm just
like daydreaming about it that is such a
random thought and has absolutely
nothing to do with this but I'm I'm
hungry so let's go inside because the
table probably is
ready okay guys I'm back home it's time
to reset the house because this place is
honestly a disaster it's giving me kind
of the ick the dishes itself just
stresses me out but also there's like
cat fur all over the couch like I know I
need to vacuum it I need to change the
sheets on my bed there's just like
things that are making the house feel
very undone I think while I do this
Renee is going to take care of the patio
and clean the patio cuz there's like
dirt all over it it's pretty early still
well it's 3:00 um but I don't think this
should take me very long my resets
usually take me like an hour an hour and
a half but this just gets me ready for
the week it makes me feel so refreshed
I'm going to film a little Tik Tok of me
doing it as well because they're just
satisfying to watch oh I have some
Amazon packages that were sitting at my
door I don't know if this is going to
look horrible but I got these little
hydrangeas they're fake oh they feel
real that's crazy cuz hydrangeas
themselves are not kitty safe but I want
to put these in like little vases on my
nightstand and like around my room I
just think it's going to be super cute
on like a little tiny vase so I just
wanted to get some fake ones because I
love fresh flowers but a lot of them are
not cat safe and Theo loves to eat
flowers like it's his food plus you
don't have to replace them and they're
just going in my room so I'm going to
put those in a vase but I need vases so
maybe we'll go to Target after this if I
finish I'm excited about this yay I
literally ordered this last night and
it's already here this is a little lamp
that I got I actually ordered two the
other one's not here yet but the reason
I like this is because I'm trying to
like I told you guys earlier add more
little like Decor touches to the house I
love the like traditional home like
hints of Nancy Meers aesthetic just
hints cuz like Ralph Lauren aesthetic
home decor I just realized within the
past few months since moving in here
that that is like what I love and that's
what makes a home feel cozy to me I
think in my apartment it was different
because I wasn't decorating it as if it
was my home it was more of just like my
Pinterest girly temporary apartment but
since I've moved in here like I
obviously want to get Decor that's long
term and so I decided to get this little
lamp from Amazon cuz I feel like it
gives that Vibe it actually feels like
really nice quality it's like pretty
heavy um this is a battery powered one
which isn't I mean a rechargeable one
which isn't like my favorite cuz I have
some like I have one in my kitchen
that's rechargeable and I just like
forget to charge it but they are still
like a really nice option for when you
don't want to have it plugged into an
outlet I was going to put this one in
the entrance oh it's so cute see you see
how it's giving that like traditional
home Vibe I love it and then with these
yes but I thought it would be cute like
like somewhere over
here should I put it in my room I feel
like it's so adorable and it would look
super cute in the bathroom I wish you
guys were here to help me in real time
see like that's super cute I might just
leave it there for now I like the idea
of it in the bathroom but I don't know
like do I need a lamp in my bathroom
like not really like am I even going to
use
that that's cute I feel like you guys
would tell me to leave it in the room
see that's cute
they look real and I think I'm going to
add some to this one as well that one
I'll probably do all white but I love
the way it looks I feel like it's just
going to bring this the space to life a
little bit more don't judge this is a
safe space this is the before look at
the dishes oh my gosh and I'm going to
make myself a little immunity drink
while I do this I'm using the amra
colostrum I drink these every once in a
while I don't do it every day cuz it's
like a strong drink but it tastes really
good so I always start in the kitchen
and then I'll like work my way around I
also might listen to some music to get
me to get the Vibes flowing
[Music]
kitchen's done actually I don't think I
ever showed you guys that I made a
coffee cart there's lots of Home updates
in this video if you're interested I
actually made a coffee cart a few weeks
ago and I never showed it and then I
have like random stuff down here I have
like a wine well half of wine and then a
prco that we got as an engagement gift
but I want this to be basically my
coffee section in this house is very
small if you guys remember my last
apartment the coffee bar was huge and I
have two coffee machines typically so I
have like my Breville which is a more
manual espresso machine love it bruise
fabulous espresso however it is time
consuming and sometimes the espresso
doesn't extract correctly it's a lot
more tedious so you kind of have to give
it a few tries sometimes my dream for
like just like a dream home or whatever
is to have a coffee bar like I loved the
section I had in my apartment so I
decided that I would create like a
coffee cart I don't know how I feel
about it it's like I like it like I do I
really like it I got this cart from
Target I think it's super cute I feel
like it matches the aesthetic of the
home really beautiful marble top with
like gold brass around there's a few
issues with this I don't know how much I
love it or how like practical it is I
feel like it is practical I just haven't
gotten to use it cuz this inpress so is
actually very broken it's just like I
don't I don't know what do you guys
think like should I make it a whole
coffee cart how should I decorate it
should I put like shelves here or is
that just like too much I'm thinking of
putting like two shelves here and doing
like a little print and like some cups
like I think it would be cute to make it
more of its own little space rather than
it just being like a random cart with a
coffee machine on it I don't know I need
to figure out what I'm doing with this
machine because I've tried everything
and it doesn't work I think it's cuz I
didn't use it for like over a year cuz
at my apartment I only used the Breville
but now I miss my espresso and it's just
not working anymore but I just thought I
would give you that update cuz I never
told you guys that I did that and I did
do that so
[Music]
I'm tired this took way longer than I
expected I guess the house was dirtier
than I remembered I've been going for
over an hour I have to go get my
groceries in like 15 minutes from
Curbside so I think I told you guys I
ordered those so I'm really just trying
to wrap it up but we still got a lot to
go
[Music]
I also got this top from maidwell
yesterday literally the most boring
thing ever but I love Basics like this
in the spring and then I like how it has
like a little slit at the bottom I just
think it'll be cute shorts jeans I love
tops you can just throw on and not think
about and then from Free People I got
this little top oh my gosh for the
summer guys it has like super cute
floral detail and then it ties on the
side over a swimsuit or with a little
bralette under that's why I got this cuz
I didn't have one it's going to be so
cute with the tan take me there also
while we're unboxing Maybelline sent me
these Teddy set tints look how pretty I
lived off of Maybelline lipstick in high
school wait should we try one
oh that's so pretty it's very matte it
feels like a mousse
[Music]
texture we are done the house feels so
clean I didn't do my closet and I have
it vacuumed upstairs but I'm just going
to have to do that when I get back but
look at how
clean and nice everything
looks the room looks so nice also I love
the way the nightstand is I mean the
dresser is coming along I think it's so
pretty sheets are in the wash going to
wash bath mats the living room spotless
okay let's go get the
[Music]
groceries I'm just going to give you a
grocery haul as I put stuff away because
I want to go to Target and it's like
6:30 and I just want to like put this
stuff away and go we have Frozen nuggets
for the week lunchtime and stuff I love
these Frozen black bean patties they are
the best ones if you're vegan or
vegetarian even if you're not I'm not
and they're really good Frozen edamame
frozen fries uh Kodiak cakes protein
waffles white rice pinto beans these are
like Essentials I always have this stuff
pickles udon noodles for stir fry uh
broccolini my favorite veggie turkey
slices for lunch sandwiches chicken
breast coconut C I ran out of this
onion Ginger
strawberries celery for the
juice stir fry veggies bananas apples
more stir Fred veggies and then I got
baby kale and burger lettuce I got a
strainer cuz I think I'm going to try
and make the green juice with my Ninja
blender cat food for Clover and I love
these chips they're my favorite right
now these Boulder batch Buffalo Ranch
[Music]
I just got back I'll show you some of
what I got cuz a lot of it's just like
laundry stuff but I I got these Easter
towels didn't find a vase for my
hydranges there just wasn't one that fit
what I need so I just need to look
online or something so they had these
towels which I love the little pink pom
poms I'm going to put these on the stove
I
think it's not a Target run if you
didn't come back with unnecessary things
I don't make the rules so I did get her
because she was so cute how could I pass
her up my squish mellow basket is
literally overflowing and that is Rene's
fault because he always buys them for me
but I love them so much and I haven't
bought one in months and then I saw the
Easter ones this is so cute if you don't
own a squish meow they are the best
pillows in the world I don't think we
should actually have regular pillows I
think we should all just have squish
mows cuz they are so unbelievably
comfortable to sleep on so if you
haven't tried that you really need to
this is the other I literally told you
guys in this video I have a PJ problem a
lot of my cute PJ sets are from from
Target in case you're wondering or you
want to know where to get cute ones the
only thing I will say is you have to be
quick like they're always sold out I got
these and they look so cute especially
for the summer I love shorts and then I
did get this bunny I think it's so cute
it extremely overpriced but it is
adorable it's probably the only Easter
Decor I'm going to put up so I'm going
to put this little guy in my room cuz I
think it's so cute the only other stuff
is I got oven mitts cuz I needed some
it's my last one caught on fire and part
of Sunday is selfcare and this is what I
love to call self-care I got some Sour
Patch bunnies I'm a sour girl are you
sour or sweet cuz I will always go for
sour yellow is my
favorite I'm going to start on dinner
I'm going to do the black bean patties
that I showed you guys because those are
super easy to make I don't feel like
feel like in every video I'm like I
don't feel like cooking a big meal
that's the story of my life these black
bean patties are so good and then I use
these burger buns from Dave's Killer
Bread I think I'm going to
like a few onions to put it on top I
think it'll be yummy and if I have
everything for animal sauce like the
In-N-Out type I'm going to make that too
throw in some of these fries into the
oven this is everything I'm using for
dinner oh also mayo and ketchup but I
need to get that from the and if you can
hear the TV I'm sorry 90day fiance is
blaring because it's the new episode and
I'm obsessed with it for some reason
[Music]
oh
it looks so good it's just the bean
burger with the American cheese burger
lettuce tomato and my little onion the
animal sty sauce and some
[Music]
fries I just sat and watched like an
hour of 90day fiance I need to watch
Like Love is Blind love Island I'm going
to do that next but it this was just
like a new episode I'm Al I'm also
watching the season of The Bachelor but
I think it sucks it's like the worst
season of The Bachelor that I've seen
and I haven't watched it in like so many
years but I used to watch it all the
time I need to shower it's Sunday night
which means it's time for me to like
reset myself and get myself ready for
the week there's not much I like to do
but I do like to do an everything shower
shave exfoliate all that good stuff
because tomorrow I'm going to want to
self tan but I'm like patching off I
don't know if you can see that yeah you
probably can see that I'm p watching off
in my self tanner from last week so I
need to exfoliate that off so I'm going
to do that I also don't know how people
shower with like all of their jewelry
like I wish I could cuz it it's cute
like it looks cute but I cannot stand
the feeling of any of my jewelry on me
when I sleep or shower I have to take
everything off so for the everything
shower I'm going to show you guys the
products that I like to use we're going
to do a little lineup cuz I'm not able
to take you into the shower with me so
I'm using the Kristen s shampoo and
conditioner and I wash my hair like
every 5ish days I would say and I love
this brand I think it's like sulfate
yeah it's sulfate free and I know that's
like the one thing you should look out
for I'm going to try this hair mask
because I don't have a good one this
one's from Lun they sent it to me a
little while ago when I did some content
with them and this is the rehab
hydrating hair mask it says to do it
after shampoo so I'm going to try this
cuz I haven't had it in shower hair mask
in so long but I miss doing them for
body I just use this verse body
exfoliating scrub which I really like
and then out of the shower I'm going to
use this oay OC the algae body oil I
love this stuff I've been using the Dr
Teal's Body Oil which I also really like
let me show it to you I like this one
cuz I just put it on like after I shower
in the shower and it's just it's like a
nice finishing step and then I think I
already showed you guys this but I'm
using the face reality bear your balance
creamy cleanser this is the shower
lineup I'll have all of it linked down
below but now I'm going to turn on the
shower take off this makeup and let's
get clean and cleansed
[Music]
I love these eye patches cuz so many
come in the pack I do them in the
morning I do them at night and it has
just been such a nice little step to add
to my skincare routine and I really do
like that these come in bulk cuz I can
use them whenever and I'm not afraid of
running out tonight I'm going to try
this mouth tape I bought it a few weeks
ago from Amazon and I just like have not
used it also make wash on
[Music]
okay so it's kind of a bit late it's
like
10:25 exactly I would like to be asleep
by this time but also if you can hear
talking it's my clock playing my
nighttime meditation it is like a bit
later than I would want it to be however
today was definitely more of like a
packed Sunday reset just like from
groceries to deep cleaning for like 2
hours to Target run cooking but I really
love the way it turn turned out anyways
I'm exhausted but I'm going to do my
little nighttime in bed things first I'm
going to gacha should we talk about
something while I gacha usually while I
do this I'll like play a YouTube video
or something what should we talk about
how have I been feeling how do I feel
today how do I feel about the week my
intentions for the week what are my
intentions for the week that's what
we're going to talk about I feel today I
feel steady peaceful my mind feels quiet
which is a good thing I had therapy this
past week for the first time in a few
weeks that was really nice I actually
have it tomorrow too my intentions for
the week I feel like to slow down I feel
like my mind goes so fast sometimes that
I just like need to seriously slow
myself down I really have tried to put
work out of my mind today and Saturday
and Sunday like I typically won't post
and I'll only film something simple like
a Sunday reset like Tik Tok there's been
like times throughout doing this that I
would like work heavily on the weekend
or edit heavily on the weekends just to
try and get more uploads up and I would
just get so burnt out and so quickly I
learned that Saturday and Sunday were
super important rest days for me and
it's such a good mental refresh for me
and I just encourage you whatever your
weekend may be completely disconnect I
really haven't been on my phone at all
today and it has just felt so nice it's
so weird cuz it's kind of like a
double-edged sword with social media for
me like I can't scroll and it ever
really be relaxing like that never
really happens for me sometimes like on
Tik Tok but because because this is my
job and because I do social media I am
never able to like fully disconnect
unless I just do not get on social media
apps at all I'm going to do a little bit
of planning right now and that's really
the extent of what I do on the weekends
when it comes to work now going into
tomorrow I don't feel burnt out I've had
my time away and I'm ready to like
tackle it again which is really nice cuz
I will get sick of it if I spend every
day on it and then I just won't want to
do my job so and if the lighting looks
very low right now it's cuz
it is I have one little lamp on in my
room I'm trying to keep it very Zen in
here it's so cute r i leaves me little
notes in my planner sometimes that I
find randomly and it's just adorable and
I love it
[Music]
okay I feel like that's kind of it for
me usually I have my whole stack of
books here if you get into bed at night
and you have a stack of books I trust
you and we can be friends that's
literally me I'm always like waddling to
bed at like 9:00 p.m. like with my stack
of books and it makes me feel like such
a grandma but I love it my clock is
playing Storm sounds and it sounds like
it's rainy outside and it's just so cozy
I'm going to try and upload this on a
Sunday and if I did successfully do that
then I really hope you enjoyed it and I
hope you did it alongside me or it
motivated you in some way or you just
had fun hanging out with me while you
laid in bed and that was your Sunday
reset cuz that's totally fine too last
week my Sunday reset was rotting for
literally 12 hours I love most about
this obviously is that it just makes me
feel so prepped and ready and I'm like
honestly the Sunday scaries are scared
of me at this point let me know if you
have any video requests there's a
reading blog coming don't worry so that
one's already taken care of cuz I'm sure
I'm going to get that one but if you
have anything else you want a certain
type of Vlog you miss the weekly Vlogs
like whatever it is let me know and I'll
see you guys next week in the next video
good night friends
[Music]